Guide to the Robert Fitzgerald Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 2.09; (5 boxes)
  - Box 91, folder 3151 (Box 119, Folder 4105)
  - Box 92, folder 3231 (Box 119, Folder 4106)
  - Box 92, folder 3232 (Box 119, Folder 4107)
  - Box 92, folder 3234 (Box 119, Folder 4108)
  - Box 93, folder 3243 (Box 119, Folder 4109)
  - Box 93, folder 3244 (Box 119, Folder 4110)
  - Box 93, folder 3253 (Box 119, Folder 4111)
  - Box 94, folder 3279 (Box 119, Folder 4112)
  - Box 94, folder 3287 (Box 119, Folder 4113)
  - Box 94, folder 3294 (Box 119, Folder 4114)
  - Box 94, folder 3311 (Box 119, Folder 4115)
  - Box 95, folder 3326 (Box 119, Folder 4116)
  - Box 95, folder 3352 (Box 119, Folder 4117)
  - Box 95, folder 3356 (Box 119, Folder 4118)
  - Box 95, folder 3365 (Box 119, Folder 4119)
  - Box 96, folder 3371 (Box 119, Folder 4120)
  - Box 96, folder 3374 (Box 119, Folder 4121)
  - Box 96, folder 3380 (Box 119, Folder 4122)
  - Box 99, folder 3447 (Box 119, Folder 4123)
  - Box 105, folder 3575 (Box 119, Folder 4124)
  - Box 105, folder 3580 (Box 119, Folder 4125)
  - Box 106, folder 3624 (Box 119, Folder 4126)
  - Box 107, folder 3631 (Box 119, Folder 4127)
  - Box 108, folder 3648 (Box 119, Folder 4128)
  - Box 108, folder 3654 (Box 119, Folder 4129)
  - Box 108, folder 3656 (Box 119, Folder 4130)
  - Box 108, folder 3657 (Box 119, Folder 4131)
  - Box 108, folder 3659 (Box 119, Folder 4132)
  - Box 108, folder 3662 (Box 119, Folder 4133)